有可能就这样跌个倒
There's a chance that I could fall
就再也起不来
and not come back
也不想怎么脱离困境
and never regret a thing
改变遥不可及
I'd never get back on track
前方浓雾一片
Darkness all around me
总让我看不著希望
I can't find the light
任由黑暗蒙蔽双眼
I let it all surround me
没试过就放弃抵抗
Giving up without a fight
痛苦心声吐不尽
The bitterness and pain inside
无数眼泪流不尽
countless tears I had to cry
我曾面对这些恐惧
I was facing all my fears
只为等你替我擦眼泪，但－－
just to let you in to dry my tears, but--
你的仁慈如此真诚
Your kindness won't betray me
我能听见你的心声
I feel your heart and soul
你的仁慈能拯救我
Your kindness still can save me
希望你不要抛弃我
I choose to not let go
伸出手，你勾住我心
Stretching out you somehow reach me
这肯定错不了
I know this can't be wrong
我准备好了，请你教我
I'm ready, won't you teach me
你的仁慈之歌
your song of kindness
看著你找到宁静
Quiet grace surrounds you
教会了我怎么自己
and helps me find my own
不知你怎么帮的
I can't tell you how you've helped me
亦或是我成长了多少
and how much I have grown
即使你是如此遥远
Even though you're far away
你开阔了我的视线
inspiration comes from you
每天都要越来越正面！
To shine a little brighter every day!
要是你能知道...
If you only knew...
我再也不会感到失落
I will never get upset
而我绝对，永远不会忘记
and I will never, ever forget
你带给我的幸福
The happiness you made me feel
好像你是真实存在般...但－－
almost as if you're actually real...but--
你的仁慈如此真诚
Your kindness won't betray me
我能听见你的心声
I feel your heart and soul
你的仁慈能拯救我
Your kindness still can save me
希望你不要抛弃我
I choose to not let go
伸出手，你勾住我心
Stretching out you somehow reach me
这肯定错不了
I know this can't be wrong
我准备好了，请你教我
I'm ready, won't you teach me
你的仁慈之歌
your song of kindness
你的仁慈如此真诚
Your kindness won't betray me
我能听见你的心声
I feel your heart and soul
你的仁慈能拯救我
Your kindness still can save me
即使你永远不会知道
in a way you'll never know
你的仁慈如此真诚
Your kindness won't betray me
我能听见你的心声
I feel your heart and soul
你的仁慈能拯救我
Your kindness still can save me
希望你不要抛弃我
I choose to not let go
伸出手，你勾住我心
Stretching out you somehow reach me
这肯定错不了
I know this can't be wrong
我准备好了，请你教我
I'm ready, won't you teach me
你的待人之道
the way to get along
即使冷风股股吹来
Even when the cold wind's blowing
即使我如此想屈服
and I want to just give in
只要听到你的歌声
It warms my heart just knowing
我就感到如此温暖
I'll hear your voice again
你何不大声唱
So won't you sing it loud
你何不继续唱
and won't you sing it long
我承诺过了，我会记得
I promise to remember
你的仁慈之歌
your song of kindness
我承诺过我会记得
I promise to remember
我承诺过我会记得...
I promise to remember...